kanoodle.com 2013-05-30

# Kanoodle - Providing Search-Targeted Sponsored Links Since 1999

At Kanoodle, we take your privacy seriously and do all we can to protect your privacy while using our site and other services available through our site. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect and use information about you as you utilize any Kanoodle services, including the adverting services we provide to businesses that have their own web sites (our "Advertising Network"). Our Privacy Policy is subject to change, so we encourage you to visit this page frequently to review our practices. By using services provided by Kanoodle.com, Inc. ("Kanoodle"), you indicate that you agree to the collection and use of your information by Kanoodle as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**Why We Collect Information**  
First and foremost, Kanoodle collects information to improve the services we provide and to present you with information and features that will interest you. We also use your information to measure our success and performance. For example, aggregate information gives us an idea of the number of visitors we attract and how they navigate our site.

**Personal Information We Collect**  
Any personal information that is collected by us is provided by you strictly on a voluntary basis. We may receive personal information from you in a number of ways, depending on the Kanoodle service you are using and your choices while using our services. Depending upon the nature of the service being provided, we may ask you for, and you may choose to send to us, your name, e-mail address, physical address or other personal information necessary to complete a transaction or provide services to you. For example, if you choose to run an advertising program through Kanoodle, we will need to collect certain personal information about you in connection with administering the program; however, we do not collect any personal information from site users in connection with our activities on sites in our Advertising Network. Wherever we ask you for personal information, we try to include a link to this Privacy Policy for your review.

**Use of Personal Information**  
As noted above, unless you voluntarily provide personal information for a specific purpose, we do not collect personal information from you. Moreover, we will never combine any personal information about a user of our site with any aggregate information we collect about that user, whether collected on our site or our Advertising Network. If you choose to provide personal information, we use your personal information to provide you with particular services that you request. For instance, we may use your personal information to contact you about advertising services that you have requested and to provide you with data about your advertising campaign. We may also share your personal information with business partners who provide services you have requested. In these cases, we will provide only the information that is needed to perform the service. If you do not want Kanoodle to share your information in this way, you can simply choose not to sign up for the service in question. By providing your email address to Kanoodle, you expressly consent to receive emails from us.

Kanoodle does not sell, trade or rent personal information to other companies. However, we will transfer personal information in connection with a sale or merger of Kanoodle or the division responsible for the services provided to you. We may also share your personal information with our technical consultants, third party auditors and other third parties who make our site available, enhance its functionality or provide associated services and/or who deal with you in processing your orders and/or delivering content, samples, products, services and gifts and prizes. These third parties are not allowed to use personal information except for the purposes of providing the applicable services. In addition, we may provide information to law enforcement authorities or pursuant to a court order or to investigate suspected fraud. Our site and services are maintained in the United States of America. By using the site and/or services, you authorize the export of personal information to the USA and its storage and use as specified in this policy.

**Aggregate Information We Collect and Use**  
In addition to personal information, we may also collect non-personally identifiable information, such as site pages viewed, browser type, computer information, cookies, clickstream data and other information. This aggregate information is analyzed and combined with similar aggregate information of other users and may be collected both on our site and on other sites in our Advertising Network. Such aggregate information is anonymous and does not identify any individual user. We may share aggregate information with our business partners and other third parties.

"Cookies" are small data files that are sent to your browser and are stored on your hard drive, keeping track of your general activity on a site. When you make subsequent visits to our site or another site on our Advertising Network, your cookie gives us a summary of your preferences and past experiences on the site. This allows us to tailor Kanoodle services to your needs. Your cookie may be altered at different times throughout your visits to a site, and it is updated frequently as you use various Kanoodle features and services. When you use the services of Kanoodle or our partners, our server may deliver certain customized information to you based on the data stored in your cookie. You may opt-out of the BehaviorTarget customized information program operated by Kanoodle's partner, Pulse 360. [Click here](http://www.pulse360.com/behavior/opt.html) to view/change your preferences for this program. You may set your browser to reject cookies; however, this may affect some functions of this site and our other services.

We may use third party advertising technology providers to serve advertisements and provide other services on this site and in connection with our Advertising Network. These services may include the use of web beacons, web bugs, action tags and third party cookies which read our cookies, or visa-versa, or involve the use of anonymous supplemental information (described below). To opt-out of other behavior targeting programs not associated with Kanoodle, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp) for the National Advertising Initiative (NAI) opt-out tool.

"Clickstream data" is a trail of electronic information that is left at each web site you visit. This information can be collected and stored by a site's server. We may, for example, use clickstream data to tell us the type of computer and browsing software you use, the address of the site from which you linked to our site, how much time you spend on each page of our site, how you navigate throughout the site and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of our users.

**Supplementation of Information**  
In order for our site to perform properly and as necessary to enhance our services, we may supplement the information we receive on this site with information from third party sources. For example, to determine if our customers qualify for credit, we may use their personal information to request a credit report. As another example, we may combine cookie data gathered on this site or on other sites in our Advertising Network with cookie data from a third party in order to improve our services.

**Other Web Sites**  
Our site may link to advertisers and other sites that collect personal information about you when you leave Kanoodle and that may have privacy policies and practices that are different from ours. This type of collection or use of information is beyond Kanoodle's control and is not covered by this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of every site you visit before providing any information.

**Security**  
Kanoodle stores all data using industry standard security devices, such as firewalls and encryption protocols, to prevent against unauthorized access to our data. We have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect. We have put in place policies to restrict access to your information by our employees. However, Kanoodle cannot guarantee that your information will be completely protected from unauthorized access and you assume such risk when you use our services.

**Corrections or Removal of Personal Information**  
This site gives users the following options for changing, modifying or deleting information previously provided. Users can email [clientservices@corp.kanoodle.com](mailto:clientservices@corp.kanoodle.com)

Users can send mail to the following postal address:

Kanoodle  
2390 North Forest Road, Suite 10  
Getzville, New York 14068  
U.S.A.  

or call the following telephone number: 1-877-KANOODLE (1-877-526-6635)

We are not responsible for removing your personal information from the lists of any third party who has been provided your information in accordance with this policy.

**Protection for Children**  
We have no intention of collecting personal information from children under the age of 13. When we become aware that personal information from a child under 13 has been collected without such child's parent or guardian's consent, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**  
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Be sure to visit this page frequently to find any updates we have made. Your continued use of the site after such changes have been posted indicates your consent and acceptance of such changes.

**Effective Date**  
This Privacy Policy is effective and was last updated on April 2, 2007.
